<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ot&#39;s Options Lab</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ot&#39;s Options Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sold an SPX Iron Condor</title>
      <link>/2022/06/23/sold-an-spx-iron-condor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/06/23/sold-an-spx-iron-condor/</guid>
      <description>I sold a 44 day SPX Iron Condor this morning for $3.30. Max risk is $6.40. This is an experiment. I will do adjustments to the trade as required.
SELL -1 IRON CONDOR SPX 100 (Weeklys) 5 AUG 22 4100/4110/3490/3480 CALL/PUT @3.30 LMT</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple PUT Vertical</title>
      <link>/2022/06/18/apple-put-vertical/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/06/18/apple-put-vertical/</guid>
      <description>The market has been dropping brutally over the last couple of weeks. It looks like it has come to a support level.
Below is a chart of Apple (AAPL), which is a proxie for the broader market. It looks like the market could go up or go sideways.
To take advantage of this situation I will sell a 29 July PUT Vertical.
SELL -1 VERTICAL AAPL 100 (Weeklys) 29 JUL 22 130/120 PUT @3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello!</title>
      <link>/2022/06/18/new-post-9-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/06/18/new-post-9-27/</guid>
      <description>Hello World!
I have finally worked out how to create and publish this blog on Netlify.
This blog is about my options trading experiment, where I will be trading with a small $500 options. The emphasis is on learning:
Learning to manage risk learning from observation This is a chart of where Apple (AAPL) ended up at the close today:
This is an Risk Profile of an AAPL Calendar trade that I&amp;rsquo;m evaluating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning to trade - test post</title>
      <link>/2022/06/18/learning-to-trade-test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/06/18/learning-to-trade-test-post/</guid>
      <description>Learning to trade as a path to self discovery and personal growth This is something quite unexpected! When I first became interested in learning to trade, It was primarily as a means of making money. What I learnt along the way was something much greater.
In learning to become a successful trader, I had to overcome my fears. Fear of losing money and selling too soon. Fear of losing money and failing to commit to the trade, and missing out on a big opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;ve learned as a trader</title>
      <link>/2022/06/18/what-i-ve-learned-as-a-trader/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/06/18/what-i-ve-learned-as-a-trader/</guid>
      <description>Trading options is a risky business. When I first learned to trade options I was so scared of losing my money that I didn&amp;rsquo;t trade options for a long time.
The options course that I took, focused on buying options. As on options buyer, you have to get the market direction right to be able to make a profit.
A few years after doing my options course, I learned that it was more profitable to sell options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/2020/12/01/hello-r-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/12/01/hello-r-markdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Plain Markdown Post</title>
      <link>/2016/12/30/a-plain-markdown-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 21:49:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/12/30/a-plain-markdown-post/</guid>
      <description>This is a post written in plain Markdown (*.md) instead of R Markdown (*.Rmd). The major differences are:
You cannot run any R code in a plain Markdown document, whereas in an R Markdown document, you can embed R code chunks (```{r}); A plain Markdown post is rendered through Blackfriday, and an R Markdown document is compiled by rmarkdown and Pandoc. There are many differences in syntax between Blackfriday&amp;rsquo;s Markdown and Pandoc&amp;rsquo;s Markdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>This blog focuses on my options trading experiment with a small $500 account.
The goal of the experiment is to grow the account from $500 to $5,000 by conservatively trading options in the US market. This is called the $500 challenge by some. I call it the $500 experiment.
In this experiment I&amp;rsquo;m sticking with the KISS principle. Keep It Simple.
I will only look at the SPY, which represents the broad market.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
