<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>trading on Ot&#39;s Options Lab</title>
    <link>/categories/trading/</link>
    <description>Recent content in trading on Ot&#39;s Options Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/trading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sold an SPX Iron Condor</title>
      <link>/2022/06/23/sold-an-spx-iron-condor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/06/23/sold-an-spx-iron-condor/</guid>
      <description>I sold a 44 day SPX Iron Condor this morning for $3.30. Max risk is $6.40. This is an experiment. I will do adjustments to the trade as required.
SELL -1 IRON CONDOR SPX 100 (Weeklys) 5 AUG 22 4100/4110/3490/3480 CALL/PUT @3.30 LMT</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple PUT Vertical</title>
      <link>/2022/06/18/apple-put-vertical/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/06/18/apple-put-vertical/</guid>
      <description>The market has been dropping brutally over the last couple of weeks. It looks like it has come to a support level.
Below is a chart of Apple (AAPL), which is a proxie for the broader market. It looks like the market could go up or go sideways.
To take advantage of this situation I will sell a 29 July PUT Vertical.
SELL -1 VERTICAL AAPL 100 (Weeklys) 29 JUL 22 130/120 PUT @3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello!</title>
      <link>/2022/06/18/new-post-9-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/06/18/new-post-9-27/</guid>
      <description>Hello World!
I have finally worked out how to create and publish this blog on Netlify.
This blog is about my options trading experiment, where I will be trading with a small $500 options. The emphasis is on learning:
Learning to manage risk learning from observation This is a chart of where Apple (AAPL) ended up at the close today:
This is an Risk Profile of an AAPL Calendar trade that I&amp;rsquo;m evaluating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;ve learned as a trader</title>
      <link>/2022/06/18/what-i-ve-learned-as-a-trader/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/06/18/what-i-ve-learned-as-a-trader/</guid>
      <description>Trading options is a risky business. When I first learned to trade options I was so scared of losing my money that I didn&amp;rsquo;t trade options for a long time.
The options course that I took, focused on buying options. As on options buyer, you have to get the market direction right to be able to make a profit.
A few years after doing my options course, I learned that it was more profitable to sell options.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
