<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AAPL on Ot&#39;s Options Lab</title>
    <link>/tags/aapl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AAPL on Ot&#39;s Options Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/aapl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Apple PUT Vertical</title>
      <link>/2022/06/18/apple-put-vertical/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/06/18/apple-put-vertical/</guid>
      <description>The market has been dropping brutally over the last couple of weeks. It looks like it has come to a support level.
Below is a chart of Apple (AAPL), which is a proxie for the broader market. It looks like the market could go up or go sideways.
To take advantage of this situation I will sell a 29 July PUT Vertical.
SELL -1 VERTICAL AAPL 100 (Weeklys) 29 JUL 22 130/120 PUT @3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello!</title>
      <link>/2022/06/18/new-post-9-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/06/18/new-post-9-27/</guid>
      <description>Hello World!
I have finally worked out how to create and publish this blog on Netlify.
This blog is about my options trading experiment, where I will be trading with a small $500 options. The emphasis is on learning:
Learning to manage risk learning from observation This is a chart of where Apple (AAPL) ended up at the close today:
This is an Risk Profile of an AAPL Calendar trade that I&amp;rsquo;m evaluating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning to trade - test post</title>
      <link>/2022/06/18/learning-to-trade-test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/06/18/learning-to-trade-test-post/</guid>
      <description>Learning to trade as a path to self discovery and personal growth This is something quite unexpected! When I first became interested in learning to trade, It was primarily as a means of making money. What I learnt along the way was something much greater.
In learning to become a successful trader, I had to overcome my fears. Fear of losing money and selling too soon. Fear of losing money and failing to commit to the trade, and missing out on a big opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
